babyvote.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy - Cutest Baby March 2019 - BabyVote

No purchase necessary. This promotion is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with, Facebook. You are providing your information to Pandere Limited, not to Facebook. If you click "Go to App" in the Request for Permission window that appears after you click the enter button, you will be providing ongoing consent to the BabyVote application, which may offer other sweepstakes and contests in addition to this one. You may change this consent at any time through your Facebook Privacy Settings.

We have created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to providing full disclosure as to how we provide services and value to you and how we may utilize the information that you furnished to us or that we obtain from you through modern technology. Your participation through our web site in any of the services or products that are unavailable through our web site shall be deemed to constitute your understanding and acceptance of this privacy policy. 

We may modify the terms of this privacy policy from time to time, so you should review it frequently. Each time you visit our web site or provide us with information, you are accepting the most current terms of our privacy policy. As in most cases of e-commerce, whenever you visit our web site your IP address and the web page from which you came are automatically collected. Using your IP address to help us identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you and enables us to optimize and administer the web site for you and to diagnose problems with our site, so we utilize your IP address for those purposes. Also as in most cases of e-commerce, our website uses cookies to monitor your experiences with our web site and to keep track of your purchases and other activities. Cookies also enable us to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password, and, if you choose, to save other personal and financial information so you do not have to re-enter it every time you visit our web site. Most browsers will provide assistance to enable you to disable cookies if you wish, but that may also disable your access to certain areas of our web site, so we do not recommend that you disable cookies.

### Collection and Use of Private Information

We collect the following types of Private Information about you from the following sources:

  * Information we may receive from you on sign-ups, membership or other forms, i.e. your name, location, e-mail, phone, and family demographic

  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others, such as your entry to contests and registration for information and services. In order to provide you with related product and service offers, we may disclose Private Information about you with trustworthy and reputable third parties such as:

  * Product-related businesses that we deem appropriate to cross-promote and create marketing partnerships with.

  * Non-product related, but value oriented values and incentives we deem valuable to our member.

  * Use for identity recognition and verification

  * Others

Although registration and/or the furnishing of personal information is not necessary in order to visit our web site, if you register or wish to take advantage of the products and services that we offer you will have to provide certain personal information. If you do submit any information, it will or may be used/ shared as stated in this privacy policy or as otherwise permitted by law. We may use your personal information in order to contact you for the purposes of providing site updates through our BabyVote newsletter, third party products or services we believe to be of interest to you, responding to requests for information, and advising you of changes to our service or other matters related to the use of our web site. We may use your provided information for any and all marketing purposes such as special offers from partners, coupons and information that we deem relevant to you as a BabyVote member or for the operation of our web site for an unlimited time period. These forms of contact may include direct mailing, phone calling, e-mailing or text messaging or otherwise. Regardless of any of the foregoing, we will not share your billing or credit card information with any other parties, except in connection with such activities as may be reasonably necessary in order to process your transactions, such as credit card servicers, receipt or support services, customer relationship management services, order or fulfillment services, shippers and other carriers and delivery services, and the like. We use reasonable security methods to contact all data that we collect and store, including but not limited to personal information, demographic information, and financial information. However, we cannot and do not insure that our systems are impenetrable or that data is not intercepted while being transmitted to or from us over the Internet or by other means. In the event we sell or transfer all or a substantial portion of our assets, then we reserve the right to transfer to a third-party any and all data and information that we have obtained or have stored. We also reserve the right to disclose any and all information and data that we have obtained or have stored to appropriate law enforcement authorities if we reasonably suspect that a user of our web site or of services or products made available through the use of our web site is engaging in or has engaged in any illegal activity.

By selecting to opt in to this service I agree for my information to be sent to and used by Austinshire Partners LLC who run Jobs For Mum and Mint19. Their full terms can be found [here](http://jobsformum.co.uk/privacy-policy/)

### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this site and providing us with your information, you agree to BabyVote.com Privacy Policy and all of the Terms set forth in this document and in Terms of Conditions and Terms of Use documents. If you do not agree to this policy and the terms, you are not granted the license to use this site or any of the services or products provided and please do not use our site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy or these terms at any time. Please check this page frequently for changes. Your continued use of the BabyVote.com site means you accept those changes in effect as of the date and time of your latest usage. You can e-mail us with any further questions you may have at [support@babyvote.com](mailto:support@babyvote.com)

VOID WHERE PROHIBITED AND/OR RESTRICTED BY LAW- all participants in or outside UK must comply with their local laws. Last modification date of these terms and privacy policy is September 04, 2016.

### Cookies policy

When we provide services, we want to make them easy, useful and reliable. Where services are delivered on the internet, this sometimes involves placing small amounts of information on your device, for example, computer or mobile phone. These include small text files known as cookies. They cannot be used to identify you personally, cannot carry viruses, or install malware.

#### What is a cookie?

A cookie is a piece of data sent to your device from a website. This means the website can recognise your device if you return to the same website. Cookies do not contain any personal information about you and cannot be used to identify an individual user. A cookie often includes a unique identifier, which is an anonymous number (randomly generated) and is stored on your device. Some expire at the end of your website session; others remain on your computer for longer.

These pieces of information are used to improve services for you through, for example:

  * enabling a service to recognise your device so you don't have to give the same information several times during one task, e.g. filling out a web form or a web survey

  * recognising that you may already have given a username and password so you don't need to do it for every web page

  * measuring how many people are using services, so they can be made easier to use and there's enough capacity to ensure they are fast

  * analysing anonymised data to help us understand how people interact with the different aspects of our online services so we can make them better

You can manage these small files and learn more about them from this article, Internet Browser cookies- what they are and how to manage them.

For more information about cookies or if you would like to learn how to remove cookies set on your device, visit: [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)

#### Cookies used on this website

This website uses both first and third party cookies. All the cookies on this site are identified below and categorized according to whether they are first or third party.

##### First party cookies

Purpose: Session management. These are ?session-based? cookies used in order to ensure the smooth running of users? sessions. This classification includes remembering your selections or preferences that you?ve already made when looking at information or using a service

Benefit: To remember your selections or preferences that you?ve already made when looking at information or using a service on the site. To make it easier to log in again if you choose Remember me.

##### Third party cookies

We use suppliers who may also set cookies on their websites' on their behalf.

##### Google Analytics:

Purpose: Web Analytics/metrics. This category comprises cookies used to evaluate site performance in terms of number of visits, unique visitors, drop-off rate for transactions etc. We measure numbers and volumes of visitors to different parts of our site and this helps us ensure the service is fast and available when you want it. It also helps us ensure that different pages on our site are useful and easy to find.

Benefit: So service is available when you want it and fast.

We will not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you.

However, if you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by our websites, or indeed any other website, you can do this through your browser settings. The ?Help? function within your browser should tell you how.

Alternatively, you may wish to visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) which contains comprehensive information on how to do this on a wide variety of browsers. You will also find details on how to delete cookies from your machine as well as more general information about cookies.

Please be aware that restricting cookies may impact on the functionality of our website.

If you wish to view a cookie's code, just open your cookie file in your browser and click on a cookie to open it. You'll see a short string of text and numbers. The numbers are your identification card, which can only be seen by the server that gave you the cookie.

For information on how to do this on the browser of your mobile phone you will need to refer to your handset manual.

To opt-out of third-parties collecting any data about your interaction on our website, please refer to their websites for further information.
